# 最近为女性朋友做了一个可以自动涂抹精华液的装置
Recently I've invented a tool for ladies to apply facial essence on their face
# 下面，我给大家演示一下。
Next I'll demonstrate how to use it
# 首先把精华液放入设备中。
First load facial essence into the equipment
# 然后合上闸就可以了。
next we close the circuit then we are ready to go
# 它能自动把精华液滴入假手中。
it automatically puts facial essence on the these fake hands
# 我的脸比较大，所以说滴两次。
my face is larger than the average, so I've put two drops on the hands
# 滴完之后开始上脸抹匀。
next we spread it evenly on my face
# 出完之后再轻轻的拍打面部 这样有助于精华液的吸收。
gently pat it all over the face until it is absorbed
# 演示完毕
That's it
# 用完之后感觉脸还是挺水润的。很润
My face feel well moisturized after this process
# 家里自行车的减震不是特别好，
The suspention system on this bike isn't very good
# 我准备把这个辐条换成弹簧的看看效果怎么样？
I'm going to replace these spokes with springs, let's see how it goes